coschedule.com 2016-06-27

# Privacy

Last Modified: 11/7/14

CoSchedule LLC ("CoSchedule" or "We") respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy. This policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit the website coschedule.com including all related webpages (our "Website") and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting and disclosing that information. Terms not defined in this policy are defined in the [Terms of Use](http://coschedule.com/terms).

#### What information do we collect and how do we collect it?

We collect both personal and non-personal information from and about website visitors. Personal information may include your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. Non-personal information is information that is about you but individually does not identify you, such as information about your internet connection, the equipment you use to access our Website, and usage details. 

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form, connect your website or blog to our Website or the CoSchedule services, or otherwise when you directly provide it to us. We also collect information automatically as you navigate through the site. Information collected automatically may include usage details, IP addresses and information collected through cookies and other tracking technologies.

#### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To present our website and its contents to you
  * To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us
  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To improve our Website (we continually strive to improve our Website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
  * To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, or to otherwise protect our rights or those of third parties
  * To comply with applicable laws, regulations, and legal process
  * To process transactions 
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
  * To provide you with notices about your [account/subscription], including expiration and renewal notices.
  * To send periodic emails 
    * The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.  
_Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email._
  * In any other way we may describe when you provide the information.
  * For any other purpose with your consent. 

#### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. 

Due to the nature of the Internet and online communications, however, we cannot guarantee that any information transmitted online will remain confidential. We are not liable for the illegal acts of third parties such as criminal hackers.

#### Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information).

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

#### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We will only share your personal information with third parties as outlined in this Website Privacy Policy (in its current or future form) and as otherwise permitted by law.

We share and give access to personal information to our employees and agents in the course of operating our businesses. For example, if you sent us an e-mail asking a question, we would provide your e-mail address to one of our employees or agents, along with your question, in order for that person to reply to your e-mail.

We may share personal information with trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. For example, we may hire a vendor to help us send and manage e-mail.

We may share personal information with a successor if all or part of our business is sold, merged, dissolved, acquired, or in a similar transaction, or in the event of a corporate reorganization. 

We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. 

However, because non-personal information does not identify who you are, we do not limit the ways we may use or share non-personal information. Non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

#### Reviewing Your Information

If you have an account with us, then you may log on to your account to view certain personal information we have regarding you, and in certain cases you may revise this information. View the “Sign In” or similar page for this capability. If you are concerned about information beyond what appears on your account-page, please contact us as described below. 

#### Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

#### Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

#### Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website [here](http://coschedule.com/terms).

#### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our online [privacy policy](http://coschedule.com/privacy).

#### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. We encourage you to periodically check back and review this policy so that you always will know our current privacy practices.

#### Do Not Track Disclosure 

This website does not monitor for or behave differently if your computer transmits a “do not track” or similar beacon or message.

#### Children’s Information

We do not intentionally collect any personal information from children under the age of 13 through this website. This website is not directed towards children under 13. If you believe that we have collected personal information from a child under the age of 13 through this website, please contact us. 

#### U.S. Audience

This site is intended for a United States audience. If you access this site from outside the U.S., you acknowledge, agree, and consent that any information you provide, including any personal information, will be transferred to and processed by a computer server located within the U.S., and subject to U.S. laws and regulations. Further, if you access this site from outside the U.S., you acknowledge and agree that you are responsible for compliance with any applicable local or national laws, rules or regulations applicable to such use.

#### California Privacy Rights.

California Civil code § 1798.83 provides certain rights to California residents, including the right to request information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for marketing purposes. To request such information, please contact us as described below.

#### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.   

* * *

CoSchedule LLC  
318 E Broadway  
Bismarck ND, 58501  
support@CoSchedule.com
